(Sheldon:)It's a
re-writable CD.
(Raj:)Just put it in.
(Howard:)Beyonce? Really?
(Raj:)She's curvy and she owns it.
(Raj:)I like that.
(Wagner's "Ride of the
Valkyries" plays)
(Leonard(as Ride of the Valkyries begins):)Oh, yeah, I'm feeling it.
(chuckles)
(Sheldon:)We are winged fury!
(Sheldon:)Which is still no excuse
(Sheldon:)for going over
the posted speed limit.
♪ ♪
(Howard:)Next time we go to
kick someone's ass,
(Howard:)we take the train.
(Sheldon:)I always prefer the train.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, let's go.
(car door closes)
SHELDON:
Coming.
(Howard:)Why did you bring that?
(Sheldon:)No weapon strikes more fear
into a man's heart
(Sheldon:)than a Klingon bat'leth.
(Leonard:)Okay, let's get
clear on something.
(Leonard:)We're just going to tell
this guy to transfer all of